Can you elaborate
on what you were saying?
Oh, my God.
I don't want her to elaborate.
Listen, I have
no problem elaborating.
Please, 'cause I'm gonna need
some details.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay, so...
It's not like
it's rocket science or nothing.
I just, you know,
I pee on him.
He likes to be peed on.
- Ew.
- And he pays you?
Girl, yes.
- He paid for
your ticket out here?
- Yes.
- And how much he pay you?
- Oh, my God, y'all.
- Please.
- 6,000.
- Damn. Really?
- Girl, these French niggas
is wild out here.
- Listen.
- Just for some pee-pee?
- Yes.
It ain't like
he collecting it.
Okay. Men have needs, okay?
And I don't kink shame,
because we are where, ladies?
We are where?
- En français?
- En français. Paris.
Clink, clink.
Thank you, Candice, girl.
For including me and my cousin
and...
bringing us on your, uh,
"business trip."
- It's business.
I feel like we needed
this little girls' trip.
- True.
- I missed y'all crazy-asses,
so...
- Aw.
- I missed you, too.
- Salud.
Salud. What's that mean?
It's like "cheers."
A European cheers.
European cheers. Okay.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay, so, what's popping?
Like, what are we
about to get into?
- This is my first time out here.
- Okay.
So, there is
this Black historical walk
that I read about.
And you follow, like,
Langston Hughes,
- Josephine Baker...
- Girl, no.
- Okay.
- Um, Candice, can we do,
like, something fun?
Can we get into something crazy,
please?
- Please.
- Trust me-- well, I want to.
But it's a little tough, 'cause
you kind of have to know a local
to, like, really get
into the crazy stuff.
- Really?
- Then why don't you call
your pee-pee boy?
- Right.
- No.
What?
- Oh, my God.
- What's going on?
What?
Girl, where are you going?
The hell?
Van?
Hey.
Van, it's me. It's Candice.
- Non... Non.
- No?
Désolée...
Candice!
I'm so sorry, chérie.
It is so good to see...
to see you.
Et voilà.
Bon, you know,
I never got your names.
- Shanice.
- I'm Xosha.
Oh, c'est très joli.
I love it.
So wonderful to meet you both.
I will get us something
to celebrate.
S'il vous plaît,
make yourself comfortable.
Who is she?
She your friend?
Yeah, back in Atlanta.
You mean she ain't French?
Girl, no.
- This girl crazy.
Oh.
This is cute.
Et voilà.
I have a Domaine Chariot.
Hey, uh, who is this?
That is Marcel,
my partner, of course.
What-- How long have you been
out here?
Well, we met when I was working
at his restaurant.
I was running the food.
Of course, he was the chef.
And, uh...
I was such an idiot
when I first came here.
So lost and alone,
but then we met,
and we were like magnets,
you know.
Passion magnets,
which I know you understand.
Well, um, do you need any help
in the kitchen? We can catch up.
What are you doing in Paris,
actually?
She came out here
to pee on some nigga.
Oh, là l.
Uh, came out here to do
more than that.
But maybe we can catch up
in private really quick.
You know, this reminds me...
I think I am running late.
Ah, bon.
I am running late.
I have some errands to run,
but, um...
Well, you are all welcome,
of course.
I have, uh, friends. They are...
How do you say? Uh, very cool.
Yes. They will show you
a good time.
So, yes, let us go.
Seize the day.
Ooh.
Bonjour. Bonjour.
She really got
to take this bread
- everywhere we go, huh?
Maybe it's security bread,
like she don't feel French
without it.
Just need to pick up some keys
from my friend.
It should take five minutes.
Girl, this place is nice.
- Right?
- It's fancy.
- Oh, hey, stranger.
- Hello, how are you?
Mm...
- Good to see you.
- Brought some friends.
Come on in.
- Hey, guys. Hi.
- Hi.
- Oh, my God.
Welcome to my suite, my sweets.
- All right, sit--
Oh, sorry about
all the mess in...
- Oh, this is embarrassing.
Here we go, mademoiselle.
- Mademoiselle.
- Nice.
I'm Alex, by the way.
- Yes.
- We know who you are.
- Very nice to meet you.
- Hey.
- Missed you.
How good is this song?
I've been listening to it
on repeat all day.
Ashanti! Mm.
Is she still with Nelly,
by the way?
I don't, I don't think so.
- I love this song.
- It's good, huh?
- Yeah.
I had this crazy idea that...
Hey, how-how about we...
just, uh, get naked.
Take our clothes off.
I don't-- I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I get these, like, crazy ideas.
Like, so random
and completely inappropriate.
I apologize. It's...
We don't want to do that.
Right?
- I'm down. I like it.
- We can. Go ahead. Go ahead.
Stay at the door.
Make sure he doesn't come in.
Hey.
When the hell did you start
fucking Alexander Skarsg ård?
What?
When did you start fucking
Alexander Skarsg ård?
I would appreciate it
if you didn't ask me
this kind of question.
He's very private
about his sex life.
Okay. I'm just saying...
What happened to your partner?
Oh, don't be so judgmental.
You know
the strongest relationships
have blurred lines.
You should know this.
Don't be so American about this.
Van, what is that?
- It's nothing.
- You can't do that.
- Van...
- Relax. It's fine.
We do this every week.
No, Van, this is, like, crack.
You can't just...
He loves when I play games
with him.
Ah! Here are the keys.
Okay. Let's go.
Okay, ladies, um, time to go.
- What? No.
You-you didn't even touch
your Negroni.
Ladies, please!
Hey, guy-guys, no. Please stay.
Guys.
That was fun.
I loved you on True Blood.
We loved watching you dancing.
You're cold, Vanessa!
Cold!
It's Alexander.
He's doing drugs again.
I think it's meth,
but I can't be sure.
You have to call the police
or securité or someone.
What are you doing?
Go back to his room.
You know, he could die if you
stay here! You have to run!
Allez-y! Run, please!
It's our last chance
to save him!
What the fuck was that?
Oh, darlings, don't worry.
It is just a little game,
you know.
We do it, like, every week.
It is so totally fine.
It's like our little
devil dance, you know.
Xosha knows the devil dance.
Anyway, I have
another stop to make,
but if you want to come again,
I am having a party tonight.
It should be, uh, très fun.
- I mean, I'm down.
- Shit, ain't like we got
anything else to do.
- So yeah.
- Yes. Let's go.
Come, just one more stop.
Here we are.
It is nice, no?
Vanessa,
this feels like Candyman.
It does, doesn't it?
I-I think we'll just wait
out here.
I wouldn't.
She really ain't
put this bread down once.
- I fucks with it now.
Ew, that garbage smells
like something died in it.
That is not
how dead things smell.
O-Okay, look, Van.
Can we please talk?
Because I'm being serious
right now.
- You're really starting
to scare me.
What is so scary?
You wanted to see Paris.
Voilà. We're in Paris.
- Tarrare!
- What was that?
- Hey, what was that?
- It's nothing. Relax.
- Did she say "tarrare"?
- I don't know.
- It sounded like a bird.
- Look, okay,
whatever's going on,
we can talk about it, okay?
We can have some drinks,
go back to the hotel room.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- What?
Emilio.
He fucked me.
- He really fucked me.
- Hey, who's Emilio?
Okay, who cares? Can we please
just get out of here?
- 'Cause I really don't
feel safe.
- Is Emilio the plug?
Is this drugs, Van?
Are you selling drugs?
Well, let me get some Molly,
then.
- Tarrare!
Shit.
We have to go.
Merde.
Fucking Emilio.
Wait-wait, what--
what's happening?
- Like...
- Tarrare!
Who are these guys?
Van, Van. What do they want?
There's nothing more I can do.
If this is the way...
...this is the way.
Tarrare.
Okay, why do they keep
calling you Tarrare?
He was the man
who ate a baby.
Viens, viens!
Come on.
Where are we going?
She hasn't said anything
this entire time.
I know, she seems mad.
Is she okay?
No. She's not. Van!
Oh, shit.
Come on.
The fuck?
- Chéri, ça va?
- Mwah, mwah. Mon bébé.
I'm so glad you texted me.
I was losing my mind in there,
you know?
- Bien sûr.
- Long day.
But you can visit any time.
- Ces sont tes amies?
- Oui.
Candice, Xosha et Shanice.
- Salut.
-  È belle.
You know, I have an engagement
present for you and Emilio.
I have to give it to you both,
because I missed your party.
No, you're always so thoughtful.
- We missed you, you know.
- I know. It's so sad.
Alors, I haven't seen Emilio
in...
...forever.
Do you know where he is?
Bébé, what luck.
- Emilio is inside!
- Non, ce n'est pas vrai!
He has also come for a visit.
Could we say a quick hello?
- Of course.
- Okay, come on. On y va.
- My love.
Look who has come to visit.
Salut, Emilio.
Look, okay.
Please, I am sorry.
It's a misunderstanding.
I-I have the package, but...
but the package is
for someone else.
Did Delphine ring you?
On, no, sh-sh-she was
supposed to ring you.
- Is this true, Emilio?
- What's going on?
Oh, nothing, my lion.
Uh, I promise.
Carlos, can you get someone
to bring us some wine
and some cheese?
Oh, and for her friends,
whatever they want.
- No. No.
- Wine? Yeah?
I think we will be just fine
with some, uh, pain?
Bread?
Okay, okay.
Okay, everyone.
Please, everyone, go.
Merci. Merci.
Please. Please, please.
Please, you know me.
Come on, Van, you know me.
If you leave a baguette
sitting out for a week...
...you're crazy.
Why would you?
It would get stale.
And hard.
But what if you leave it out
for two weeks?
Or three weeks?
Or... or six months?
How hard and how stale
would it become?
- Oh, my God!
- It was worth the wait.
- Oh, my God.
The bread was worth the wait.
- Okay, okay, Van, Van, please.
- Where... is the package?
- Please. Van, please.
- Oh, all right.
- I mean... All right, all right.
Emilio.
Where is the package?
I...
I can get you another bundle
tomorrow.
Oh, no. Today, Emilio.
- Van, please!
- Open your mouth.
Huh?
Either way, you will have
to open your mouth.
Whether it is to tell me
about the package,
or to sink your teeth into this.
All right, all right. It's...
It's in the vase. The vase.
Shanice, retrieve the package.
No, the other vase.
- Just grab it, please.
- Okay, bet.
Vas-y, vas-y. Come on.
Emilio...
don't come to dinner tonight.
Carlos, I am so sorry.
Shall we, ladies?
It's drugs, isn't it?
We were beginning to worry.
Well, I had some surprise
friends from out of town come.
We have extra seats.
Please stay for dinner.
- Oh, no, no, no.
We won't be staying.
- What? Why not?
Uh, give me a second.
Um, because we weren't invited,
Xosha.
She just invited us.
Okay, and we had
a really long day
that we need to recover from.
Okay, well,
we was just talking about--
this morning,
you was complaining about,
"There's nothing
really fun to do,"
- and...
- Yeah. You were saying how
to find the cool stuff
we have to know a local.
Boom, there go some locals.
Something is wrong, all right?
I know this is all fun and games
to y'all,
but there is something seriously
wrong with Van right now.
Girl, let her live her life.
Yeah, I mean,
she ain't hurting nobody.
I mean, okay,
she's hurting people,
but they're seemingly people
who deserve to be hurt.
She has blood on a baguette
that she's carrying around.
You're only saying that
because you don't know her.
Yeah, we don't,
but I like whoever this is.
- I'm-a go grab a drink.
- Yeah. Me, too. Sorry, girl.
Hey, excuse me.
- Can I talk to you?
- Oh.
Bravo.
You really fucked me back there.
Paparazzi got ahold
of the story.
I might lose
the Baby Shark movie now.
Don't you ever do that again.
Let's go meet Marcel.
Think you can just
humiliate me like that?
Huh?
- Hey, Van.
- Ça va, chéri?
- Et toi?
- Oh, Marcel.
Mm.
I missed you.
Ah, where the fuck were you,
huh?
Emilio, he really fucked us
this time.
- I'm not doing it again.
Oh, before I forget,
this is my friend, Candice.
We both met while we were
stripping on that river cruise.
- Oh, of course.
We need to talk. Right now.
Uh, you want to talk?
Yeah. What the fuck is going on?
Merci.
What, you don't
approve of my lifestyle?
No. No. You're done...
You're done making me feel
like I'm crazy.
Okay, 'cause today was
nowhere near normal, Van.
Oh, mon Dieu.
Does Earn know you're here?
Does anyone know
that you're here?
Does your parents know
that you're here, Van?
Because don't think I didn't
clock your phone blowing up.
What? A very busy woman cannot
receive many phone calls?
God, can you just please
talk normal?
- I am talking normal.
- Without the fake accent, Van.
What are you doing?
Really, like,
what-what are you doing here?
What are you doing here?
Peeing on some guy?
No, it's-it's very interesting.
You know, I know you, Candice.
I know you like to be
the fancy one.
I know, uh...
God forbid anybody tries to be
more interesting than you.
Or anybody tries to do anything
that is, uh,
not worth your approval.
And the only reason you're angry
with me right now is
because you're not
in control of me.
Is that not true?
Because you're so in control,
right?
You're so in control, you almost
beat a man to death
- with a fucking baguette, Van.
- Van? Again?
Enough, please.
Marcel, are these ready?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Are those hands?
We've been chasing hands
all day?
Yeah.
I will keep my remarks brief
and in English
for those of our foreign guests.
Thank you all for coming.
Tonight's meal,
prepared by Marcel,
is truly a sacred experience.
If you are here, it is
because I know you appreciate
and revere life's
most beautiful experiences.
You will not be disappointed.
You all have in front of you
a napkin.
While some of you
may be familiar,
I offer a reminder.
We will eat this meal with this
napkin draped over our heads,
as is traditional
with Les Mains.
This is not out of shame,
as some may speculate.
Quite the opposite.
It is to allow a private and
sensuous moment with a meal.
A meal that I assure you
rivals even the finest banquet
at Mount Olympus.
And now,
Les Main.
Bon appétit.
Let's go.
First class.
Girl, this is
some high-end shit.
I feel like I'm in
Beauty and the Beast.
Mad exclusive.
Mm, smells amazing.
Kind of earthy.
- Hey, look.
If you want to live your life...
doing this crazy sh--
Shit, sorry.
Um... Okay.
But what about your old life?
Change is good, Candice.
Yeah. But, I mean,
what happens
when your visa runs out?
Marcel and I,
we will get married.
It's easy.
Okay.
Have you talked
to your parents?
They're going to be thrilled
for me.
They've always wanted me
to get married.
They've always wanted
to visit Paris.
Hmm.
And money?
I am working, as you can see.
And Lottie?
Where does she fit
into all this?
I'm going to, uh...
bring her here.
With me.
Uh...
to eat hands?
Get out.
- Get out!
- No, no, no, no, no.
- No, no, no, no. No, no, no, no.
- No, no! Please, Van!
- Get the fuck out of here!
- What the fuck
are you doing?
- Van?
- Get out!
Van, stop! Arrête!
- Arrête!
What the fuck am I doing here?!
- What?!
Uh-uh-uh. You hear that?
Yeah, what is that?
Oh, my God, girl.
This is... this is a hand!
- Bitch, this is a whole hand.
- Oh, my God.
Y'all are eating hands!
Y'all, this is a hand. Hello?
- That's fucking gross.
- Oh, my God.
We need to get the fuck
up out of here!
- Where's Candice?
- These people are crazy.
Come on. Come on, come on,
come on.
Eating hands, shit!
All right!
I'm starving!
Where are these little hands?
I want to see Lottie.
Where's Lottie?
- Where's Lottie?
- Van.
- Hey, okay.
All right, we can find her.
- I know.
I've just been feeling
really off for a while.
I don't really know
for how long, but...
Couple weeks ago,
I was driving in Atlanta and...
this dark feeling came over me.
I, uh...
I...
I closed my eyes.
I closed my eyes
while I was driving.
And then I got... got scared,
so I opened my eyes,
and I was in the opposite lane.
And...
once I realized
what I was doing...
I just cri-cried
all the way home.
And I just, I thought about...
How I'm a... I'm a terrible mom.
And when I picked Lottie up
from school,
I just f-- I felt like
she was looking at me,
like... like she knew
what happened.
And that she hated me for it.
That I would do that to her.
So I...
I brought her to my mom's,
and I bought a ticket to Europe.
I don't even remember
that flight.
I just, I was just...
blacked out.
And I land in Amsterdam.
Like, what the fuck am I doing
in Amsterdam?
And I couldn't sleep.
You know, this jet lag and...
I was watching TV all night,
and I...
And then...
Amélie came on.
And then I was like,
I want to be,
I want to be Amélie,
and I came here.
And I couldn't... I couldn't...
Couldn't do that, either.
Well...
That's because you're cooler
than Amélie.
I'm not cooler than Amélie.
Yes, you are.
I don't even know who I am.
You know who you are.
Earn knows who he is.
Lottie knows who she is.
But who the fuck am I?
I don't even know.
You're somebody.
I-I don't know. That's...
Oh, my God.
You're gonna be okay.
Okay.
Don't you have to pee
on someone?
Yes, I do.
He'll be fine.
I need to go home.
Let's go home.
Hello?
Uh, hi.
Nice.
You can put your things
by the door.
May I offer you some champagne?
Cheese or grapes?
No, I had, like, two bottles of
Powerade for lunch.
Let's just do this.
Yeah. Of course.
Stop.
- Hey.
- Earnest Marks?
- Yeah.
- Sign here.
- What's this?
- It's your bag.
I got all my bags.
- Your name Earnest Marks?
- Yeah.
- You travel on May 8?
It's your bag. Sign here.
I know this is not my bag.
Cool. Have a nice day, bro.
Hmm.